Are you all ready to be dyed in Luli's colors?
Yes!
Thank you very much.
I am Ruri Shiraishi, a first-year high school student and staff researcher from Shizuoka Prefecture,
Yes, I'm Ruri Shiraishi, a first-year high school student from Shizuoka, Japan.
Choo-choo-choo, Nanoha ni Tomare.
I will research performances that will catch your attention.
I am Nanoha Aoyama, a 14-year-old junior high school student. I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
That's two of you.
And here is the other one, Tempa, who will be speaking to you. Please come in!
Are you ready to crack open the walnuts?
Yes!
Thank you very much. I am already 24 years old.
Pleased to meet you.
Now, we have Mr. Hori here.
Last time you taught us about the heart of being an idol.
And this time I was going to talk about something else.
Before that, the two of you in the hall now greeted each other as idols.
I'd like to ask Ms. Mori if she would like to introduce herself.
I see.
No, but...
I guess I'd like to introduce myself.
I think it's been a long time in the history of idols
in the history of idols, right?
Like, "Hi!
Like this.
I think it's really great that we can do that.
I think it's really great to be able to do that.
I used to make the audience get down on their knees.
Oh, I can do that.
I might get my costume a little dirty.
I'll just get down on my knees here.
Oh, how did I get undressed?
Oh, yeah.Oh, yeah.
Um, I'll tell you what.
I said it's a festival place festival.
wasshoi wasshoi wasshoi
the daughter of a tanjiri (a kind of Japanese chrysanthemum)
Kurumi-sama
Keep going down until I tell you to look up.
Here we go!
Let's go!
Festival, festival, festival!
A boy and his daughter
Kurumi-sama!
Look up!
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
I'm Tori Kurumi, thank you very much for the amazing thank you. I am Kamakura Bi. Great.
Thank you.
Thank you for showing the back of your head to the camera.
I'm so excited, my voice is really backwards.
Q. What is your best skill in this concert?
Yes, I am.
That's right.
I started out by singing a children's song called "Choo Choo,
My specialty is nursery rhymes, so I wanted everyone to know that.
Specialty nursery rhymes?
Yes, that's right.
That's amazing. I've never heard that before.
Not a folk song, but a nursery rhyme?
It's a nursery rhyme.
Wow.
What kind of skill is that?
I sing nursery rhymes.
I'm in that song now.
That's funny. I've never heard it before.Interesting. First time I've heard it.
Your best song is "Butterfly"?
Butterflies because it has seven leaves in it,
I made it that way,
My best song is called "Wisteria Mountain.
What's that?
What kind of song is it?
Can I sing it?
It's okay, right? I'll go. What song? What song? Can I sing it? It's all right.
I'll go.
It's mine.
I can't sing well.
I don't know.
I don't know the difference.
You were really good just now.
Really?
Please let me remake it.
Please do.
This is a special skill as well. Let me have a little revenge. Please. This is my specialty.
I can't decide at all.
I just wanted to give you a good song.
Thank you very much.
You're super-conscious.
I'll go. This consciousness is amazing. I'm going. Put your head above the clouds
Looking down at the mountains on all sides
Hear the Lord of Thunder below
Fuji is the highest mountain in Japan
Fuji is the highest mountain in Japan. I'm sorry. It's been so long.
They sang the full song.
But they sang it in the middle of the song.
I want to make it a chuck melody. She sang the full song well. But I couldn't do it even if I cut it in the middle.
Machiyuki-chan sang a chuck melody. She was amazing.
Which children's songs are you good at, Ruri?
Nursery rhymes?
No, I'm not a nursery rhyme idol. I'm not a nursery rhyme idol.
I'm not a nursery rhyme idol.I'm not a nursery rhyme idol.
How did you make it?
My name is Ruri,
I have a color called Ruri Iro,
I wanted everyone to dye their feelings in Ruri's color,
I made a self-introduction saying, "Are you ready to be dyed in Lurie's color? I introduced myself by saying, "Are you ready to be dyed in Lurie's color?
It's cute.
The name is only possible because of the room.
Everyone is dyed in Lily's color.
Are you dyed?
I'd like to say that you've all been dyed Lulie's color,
I'd like to go on to the main topic of the last issue. I've already done it. I'd like to say that you all have become Lululee,
Last time, I would like to go to the main topic. Yes.
Last time, Mori-senpai taught us how to be an idol.
Yes, sir.
Currently, she is also active as a reporter on a TV program.
Please give her my best regards.
By the way, do you have any tips for introducing live spots?
Apparently, but not only for spots.
When I am on location
I just try to enjoy myself.
Depending on where I go.
If it's too hot
or the food is too spicy
I'm sure there are a lot of things
I just try to have fun.
I think it's the best if people who are watching
I think that's all that matters.
But...
I think there are different types of people.
Depending on the person
Some people say you should do your research before you say it.
There are those who say it's better to say it.
Some people say it's better to do a thorough research before saying it, while others say it's better to just go with what they feel.
I'm more of a "what I ate at that time" kind of person.I'm more of a person who says what I felt at the time I ate it.
I prefer to say what I felt at the time I ate it in order.
For example, if the food looks amazing, I praise the appearance first.
Next, I praise the smell of the food before I eat it.
After you eat it
Texture and
If you're particular about it, you can say something about the seasoning.
Or the aftertaste.
In that order.
I think you'll get a good feeling.
In order
Just say it in order
And have fun.
Do you do food reports?
I've never done it before. I've never done it before,
I've done a food report for a project,
I'm a moderator.
I was the host.
So you were a spectator.
I was just watching.
This time, I asked Mr. Shirai, who was such a spectator, to do an air report,
I'm going to have Mr. Shirai, who was such an onlooker, do a report on the air,
I'm going to have Mr. Aoyama do the same,
I asked Mr. Shirai, who had been watching from a height, to do a report on the air, and I also asked Mr. Aoyama to do the same, and then I asked my senpai to give him a bad report.
Well, look at it.
I'd like to ask my senpai to show me their comments.
I'd like you to show them to me.
Do you have it?
No, I don't.
Air?
Air.
Wow!
It's the first food repo air.
It was air.
It was the first food report air.
Let's go to the live broadcast corner!Let's go to the live broadcast corner.
Reporter Shiraishi-san
Yes, this is Shiraishi.
Please take a look at this.
This Umakara Omelette Rice!
It looks a little red, but it looks huge. Please take a look. This Umakara Omurice is a spicy omelet.
It looks red, but I'm not sure if I can eat it,
I don't know if I can eat it because I don't like spicy food,
I don't know if I can eat it, but I would like to try it.
Isn't it spicy?
Yes, it is. First of all, it smells spicy,
I think it might be a little spicy,
But let's try it.
The eggs are very soft and the sauce is spicy, but it is so good that even I can eat it,
But it is so delicious that even I can eat it,
I think it is a good menu.
It's a good menu.
I can't eat spicy food,
I can't eat spicy food, but I can eat it again and again,
I can't eat spicy food, but I can eat it again and again, and it's so good that I get addicted to it.
You should try it too.
Wow!
You did a great job.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm too nervous.
It's a great show, isn't it?
It was interesting.
It looked really big. The memories.
He said he could eat it,
I thought it must have been hard for him to see his face when he ate it.
It was interesting.
I think it's important to start from the appearance of the red color.
But did you do that earlier? Maybe.
I was thinking of looking, smelling, and eating it,
Oh, that's not what I meant.Oh, that's not what I meant.
I was aware. I was aware of it. Good, good, good. Look, smell, and eat. Oh, that's not what I mean.
I was aware of it.
Good, good, good.
I'm glad the order was imaginative.
Out of 100 points
85 points!
I wish you had blown it out once.
Blow out, once.
When you eat once, and you eat spicy food, definitely once.
With a blurb.
No matter how spicy it is.
Even if it's not spicy. Yes, no, no, one time, zu, that's a lie.
I don't care how spicy it is.
It was cute.
Can you go to the scary ones?
I've never been.
Then you can't imagine.
I can't imagine it at all.
After the scripts were handed out.
I looked up "haunted house reporter.
You're cheating.
Well then, let's get to the live broadcast.
I'd like to go to the live broadcast corner today from the giant zombie house with an average height of 3 meters,
I'm sure we'll get a report from Ms. Aoyama.
This is Ms. Aoyama, our reporter!
Hello, I'm Nanoha Aoyama. My name is Nanoha Aoyama.
Today I'm here at Universal Night Japan.
Let me tell you why I look like this,
From now on, the giant zombie pavilion of the haunted house,
The pavilion.
I'd like to go to the giant zombie mansion.
The giant zombie mansion.
I've just received some information,
The average height of the zombies is 3 meters,
I am 1.63 meters tall.I'm 1.63 meters.
So, I am twice as tall.
So I'm a little scared,
I would like to go in now.
Excuse me.
What's that? Where is it? Where is it?
Oh...
Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it? Where?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What?
Your face is in the kettle.
Your face is in a kettle.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
There's hot water coming from your mouth.
Hot water is coming out of your mouth.
May I? Can I eat it?
Thank you very much.
Here's your tea.
I'm getting tea.
I'd like to try some.
It is delicious.
What a surprise, it is from Shizuoka, and it is very tasty from Shizuoka.
So, this is for Mr. Horii and Mr. Shiraishi in the studio,
I would like to take it home as a souvenir next time.
That was how I wanted to end the tour,
There is a person with a big night view face of 10 meters.
It's not a person. There is a zombie.
I thought it was a little scary,
But it is making a hot spring with hot water from its mouth.
It's not scary at all.
So, I would like to go back home, so I would like to end the live broadcast here.
Thank you very much.
Applause
I don't understand.
I gave you two point twenty-three.I scored two twenty-three.
I gave it a score of 23.
I was really enjoying the show, and I could feel the fun in the air, but the microphone got stuck in my jaw a little bit during the show, but it was kind of scary.
I was scared.
Even in the midst of the scary situation
I could feel the professionalism of your report.
I felt your professionalism.
Thank you very much.
For example, I'm not very good at sports.
I'm not very good at sports, but when I go on location for athletic events, I'm not very good at all.
But there are people like that among our clients.
I think it's important to communicate from their point of view.
I don't think it's a bad thing if they retire.
If you really can't do something, you say you can't do it.
I'm just saying that I can't do what I really can't do and that it's realistic and someone else will do it for me.
I think it's okay to have that kind of feeling.
Q. About this concert
I really enjoyed the concert, and I was able to have a lot of fun because you talked to us a lot.
Thank you very much. I hope to use a lot of your advice in my projects,
Please let me know if you have any more questions.
Of course! Drop me a line anytime.
Of course, drop me a line anytime. Oh!
But, after all, it's not often that I get a chance to consult with my seniors like this,
I'm glad to be able to consult with them as a project like this.
I'm glad that I could talk to you about it as a project,
I always respected him,
So I was very happy to be able to talk to you like this.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. It was terrifying. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I'm so sorry.
Now, how was it for you, Mr. Poppon?
Yes, it was great. I thought that there are two such great people in the current research students,
I think it's a little scary. Really.
The seniors can't afford to sit idly by. They will come any moment.
They will come any day now. These research students.It's coming any moment now. This research student.
Thumbnail zombies.
The zombie at night.
I really feel like I can't lose.
I will continue to do my best.
Thank you very much.
Well then. So, Mr. Shirai Kikayama and Mr. Hori Tatsumei. Thank you very much.
My opponent so far is Kurumi Hori,
Ruri Shiraishi, who is a research student at Statler,
Nanoha Aoyama.
Bye bye!